<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Love. Life & Action Figures]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Love. Life & Action Figures]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2016 05:25:42 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="undefinedrss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Wealthy Boy Who Had Little...]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The Wealthy Boy Who Had Little...</h1><p>My name is Larry Hohoho from Singapore, I grew up poor but in a Happy Family where my Parents are thrifty and we have no need for anything that we do not own. They have always instilled in my Sister and me the value of things, that we should not waste food and that generosity is not limited to the rich because we have always given what little we have to those less fortunate. I grew up during the days of Star Wars (Empire Strikes Back) + Indiana Jones (The Temple of Doom) and consider my childhood to be the Golden Age of Toys. Toy commercials are seen frequently on TV between cartoons and closing taglines like:"Each sold separately" & "Batteries not included" are commonly heard.Just like any other kid, I WANTED THEM ALL!!! Obviously, our family had very little budget for new toys given our financial situation then. Whatever toy we received from our Parents maximised on education values rather than fun.My father Loves to swim by the seaside and while he swims with my Sister, my Mother would take me trawling the beaches to "rescue lost Toys" which the other kids have left behind. It was like a treasure hunt mostly for plastic army men but we always took something back with us.Most of our other Toys are pass-em-downs either given to us by relatives or my Father's colleagues whose kids have outgrown or no longer played with them. We did not really care how they came about as those Toys that I grew up with were just pure GOLD. To me, a Toy is more than just a Toy. They represent and mark different parts of our wonderful childhood growing up. Now that I am a Father, I hope I will be able to pass this culture down to my children so that they will be able to appreciate the finer TOYS in Life... </p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/cd9afc33-f758-4075-809e-d9cfa5bd97e3.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/cd9afc33-f758-4075-809e-d9cfa5bd97e3.jpg</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7848d4e1-f11a-4dfd-82f9-572ce11baaf1</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2016 05:25:41 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>